Emerson Santos Lima

emerson.dev7@gmail.com

Software Engineer +55 89 99400-3153

github.com/emersonlimaa linkedin.com/in/emersonslima

ABOUT ME

I'm 23 years old and I'm in the 3rd period of systems analysis and development. I currently carry out small and medium-sized projects for people and companies in a team or individual freelance mode, these projects being integrated with React, NodeJS and React Native. I started in software development at the beginning of the pandemic where I found opportunities to develop my skills and passions within the technology field.

EDUCATION

Estácio de Sá University

January 2022 - Current

System Analysis and Development

The role of the System Analyst and Developer is to analyze, design, document, specify, test, deploy, and maintain computer systems and software.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Qualitare LTDA

Marcolândia, Piauí, Brazil

Software Engineer - Freelance Mobile

Nov 2022 - Feb 2023

Creation of the application "Me Note". I was part of the development team, where I was responsible for the mobile application.

- Developed the interface using React Native for build.
- Technologies: React Native CLI, Styled Components, React Native, TypeScript

MAIN PROJECTS PERSONAL

FeedGet June 2022

Developed so users can create application feedback from core applications.

- Developed the interface using react and react native for mobile.
- Created an API in NodeJS and database using prisma and postgresql
- Technologies: Expo, HTML, CSS, React, React Native, TypeScript, NodeJS, PostgreSQL, Vercel (deploy)

Portfolio February 2022

Website developed to showcase my main skills.

- Created the design in Figma using notions of UX and UI
- Developed the static website and deployed it on Vercel
- Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Vercel (deploy)

MeNote Nov 2022- Feb 2023

Mobile app development

- Developed the app mobile according to Ui and Ux designer.
- Technologies: React Native, Styled Componets, TypeScript, NodeJS, Expo

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

1 years: JavaScript, TypeScript

TECHNOLOGIES

HTML5, CSS3, ReactJS, React Native, NodeJS, Express, socket.io, NextJS, SQL, MongoDB (NoSQL), Git, Vercel, Heroku, /Bash, Android SDK, Expo, ViteJS, TailwindCSS, UX/UI, Styled Componentes

LANGUAGENS

Portuguese – Native English - Technical

ONLINE COURSES

FullStack JavaScript (OneBitCode, 2022), Specialization NodeJS (Rocketseat, 2022), Specialization React (Rocketseat, 2022), Specialization React Native (Rocketseat, 2022)